♪We are both dim light♪
♪Will time erase us?♪
♪Those who fade away
in the shadows silently♪
♪Also crave a life
under the bright sun openly♪
♪How can I break free
from the chains of fate?♪
♪Who whispers in my ear♪
♪That I'm bound to fall?♪
♪Then burn me♪
♪Burn my stubbornness♪
♪The surging bitterness♪
♪The hot tears♪
♪Nobody knows♪
♪Entangling in the past♪
♪Silence in the darkness♪
♪The dim light finally turns♪
[Kill Me Love Me]
♪Into the fire of rebirth♪
[Episode 16]
[Fanghua Palace]
[Brother]
I am so useless.
I promised my brother
I'd protect Mei Lin.
Your Highness.
this is not your fault.
She insisted on leaving.
How could we stop her?
But General Yin said
Prince Jing took her.
Chagu.
what if Mei Lin got eaten
by a black bear?
Your Highness.
His Majesty has already
sent people to search for her.
Maybe she's still alive.
Mei Lin doesn't seem
like an ordinary girl.
She won't get killed so easily.
Right.
She's just missing.
She's not dead.
No.
I can't tell my brother.
He's having a hard time in Xiyan too.
I can't make him worry.
Chagu.
His Majesty will find
Mei Lin alive. right?
Your Majesty. please take your medicine.
Has the search started?
Remember.
search for her
under Concubine Yan's name.
Once Mei Lin is found.
I want to be the first to question her.
Keep this from Concubine Yan.
Your Majesty.
do you suspect Mei Lin?
With secret guards around Jinghe.
this accident seems suspicious.
Many from Qingzhou
have always resented the court.
and Mei Lin is an orphan from there.
I'm worried
she has other plans.
In any case.
I want her found.
alive
or dead.
Yes. Your Majesty.
How are the preparations...
for Jinghe's funeral coming along?
According to your instructions.
everything is being handled
as a state funeral.
His Highness has taken care of it all.
[Memorial Tablet
of Prince Murong Jinghe]
Kneel!
[Tingyun Pavilion]
Prostrate!
Return to the capital immediately
and prepare for my funeral.
For my safety.
make it convincing.
Rise!
[Tingyun Pavilion]
Your Highness.
[Prince Jing's Mansion]
we've been watching for days.
Qingyan
hasn't sent anyone
to look for his master.
Could Prince Jing really be dead?
The two of them always put on a show.
In any case. I must see
Jinghe's body myself.
Send more men to search.
claiming
the target is Mei Lin.
Jinghe's greatest love.
to avoid raising Father's suspicions.
Understood.
By the way.
where is General Yin?
Of all the officials. only General Yin
hasn't paid respects
or sent offerings.
It seems
she hasn't accepted Jinghe's death.
You've caught a chill.
Go home
and brew some Tianjing Grass soup.
Got it.
Sir.
could you take a look at her?
You're awake. young lady?
I told you she'd be fine.
but you didn't believe me.
Honestly.
she looks better than you.
Give her Tianjing Grass
for quicker recovery.
Sir.
please check on my brother too.
I don't need checking.
Your brother
is quite weak.
He needs proper rest and care.
You should
have some Tianjing Grass too.
Is this Tianjing Grass a cure-all?
You outlanders don't understand.
Tianjing Grass boosts energy.
enhances circulation.
and keeps people and livestock healthy.
I'm better at medicine than he is.
If you're unwell.
let me treat you.
Luckily. Qingyan left me some medicine.
Since when did you become a physician?
- Illness makes one a doctor.
- Futian's father!
Hurry. save him!
Wei is dying!
Hurry.
Be careful.
When did he get sick?
We were hunting in the mountains
and found him unconscious by the stream.
He...
He looks like
he has the plague.
The mountain stream?
It's by the path near Sunset Cliff.
Is the stream water contaminated?
Hurry! Tie up these two outlanders!
They're carrying the plague!
Everyone who got sick
was infected by them!
They were poisoned from drinking
the mountain stream water?
Wei is in critical condition.
He may not survive without an antidote.
This poison.
developed by the Xiyan.
was used to contaminate upstream water
and kill many Yan soldiers.
I never thought
the Crown Prince
would scapegoat the Xiyan.
Can we save him?
Thunder Duke Vine
and Qingyan's medicine
can neutralize the poison.
There's Thunder Duke Vine
in the mountain.
Wait until nightfall.
If we leave now.
we won't have an explanation.
Alright.
What about the other villagers?
The mountain stream water
reaching the village
is much less toxic.
They should be fine.
It's always like this.
The common folk. clueless as ever.
always get caught in the crossfire.
They went into hiding
to escape disaster.
yet still. disaster found them.
There's a fire.
Mei Lin!
Our house is on fire!
We need to go.
- Let's go!
- Mei Lin...
Come on!
They jumped out the window! Help!
Stop running!
You two. stop!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Why are you running?
You're infected with the plague.
so we're burning herbs to ward it off.
If you don't get treated.
you'll endanger yourselves and others!
We can't let you spread it!
Exactly! You can't leave!
Listen to me.
My sister and I aren't infected.
Wei and the villagers
got sick from the mountain stream water.
I know how to cure them.
Are you
a physician?
My sister and I caught the same illness
while we were fleeing.
A traveling physician saved us
with Thunder Duke Vine.
I'm sure
it can save them too.
Can Thunder Duke Vine work?
Why...
Why should we believe you?
I can go up the mountain
to gather the herbs.
I'll go with you.
Let your sister go.
You're too weak.
Stay here as a hostage.
I'll go with them.
Let's go.
Alright. this way.
- Come on.
- Let's go gather the herbs.
Let's go.
[West Suburbs Barracks]
Luomei.
remember.
protect the nation.
And keep Great Yan safe!
Your Highness.
General Yin.
I'll practice with you.
I've lost.
If we were on the battlefield.
my dagger slipping
would have meant death by your sword.
Longer weapons have the advantage.
I fought your short dagger
with my long sword.
My victory has no honor.
A defeat is a defeat.
Everything is already decided.
Indeed.
Luomei.
these past years.
Jinghe didn't have it easy.
He wanted
to be buried in Qingzhou
with the Weibei Army.
Perhaps this way
is a release for him.
I'm just sad
Prince Jing didn't die
on the battlefield.
Forget it.
Let this dagger
be buried with him.
That dagger
was actually a gift from me.
It pairs
with this one.
When we were younger.
I knew of your feelings for him
and didn't dare compete.
so I
gave it to you through him.
I never thought I'd get to say this
or
that these two daggers would reunite.
Luomei.
in fact.
it's not just Jinghe
who can fight by your side. I can too.
I can stand with you
through life and death.
Will you
keep this dagger for my sake?
I've already decided
to bury it with Prince Jing.
Though it was a gift from Your Highness.
it holds
many memories of my time with him.
Let it carry those memories
and be buried with him.
I hope Prince Jing
can once again be
a great general in his next life.
Strike the drums for the general.
and send his heroic soul off to battle!
Luomei.
I hope this is the last time
you grieve for him.
Farewell. General!
Why aren't they back yet?
They've been gone too long.
Is that them over there?
Why aren't they back yet?
I don't know.
It really is them!
They're back!
We found it.
Here.
Boil the Thunder Duke Vine
with this medicine.
It'll work faster.
Come on. Let's get to it.
- Right.
- Let's go.
That's his sleeping powder.
It really worked!
- Thank you so much. miss!
- What a relief.
Thank you.
[Wei]
Futian's father.
What happened to me?
You were poisoned.
They saved you.
Thank you. miss.
Avoid heavy labor
for the next few days.
Madam Wang.
we'll head back now.
Alright.
Who are they?
They're siblings
who fled to our village.
They're really kind.
especially the girl.
You've got your eye on her. haven't you?
No. I haven't.
No?
Who would believe that?
Miss Mei Lin!
Miss Mei Lin.
Madam.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Are you engaged?
- No.
- Yes.
She was engaged.
but her fiance
died while we were fleeing.
Now. it's just the two of us.
After all this time.
as her brother.
I'm reluctant to let her go.
All women eventually marry.
right?
You wouldn't want
to hold your sister back.
Miss Mei Lin.
there are plenty of good men
in our village.
Take your time to pick.
I'm sure both you and your brother
will be satisfied.
It's up to my brother.
Madam Wang. here's the thing.
Once Mei Lin gets better.
we'll be on the road
to find our relatives.
It's dangerous out there.
Why don't you stay here?
Laowozi Village
is safe from war
and government interference.
with plenty of mountains and streams
to keep you fed.
If you stay. you'll have a good life.
Think it over.
We'll think about it.
Think it over. okay?
Madam.
I'm the one who makes the call.
Right.
my brother makes the call.
Alright then.
I'll go get a bed ready for you two.
A bed?
Oh. right.
You're siblings.
so you can't share the same bed.
I'll prepare two beds.
Two.
Do I really get to make the call?
I'm not as good at making up stories.
so you decide.
If only you'd always listen to me.
Come with me.
Where?
You'll see when we get there.
I saw them while gathering herbs
in the mountains.
You brought me here
to watch fireflies with you?
We're here to catch them.
not just watch.
You don't know how to catch fireflies?
♪I am still♪
♪Wandering in your eyes♪
♪March flowers scent
the hem of my dress♪
♪My worries fall like dust♪
♪Drifting toward a sea of longing♪
♪How I look forward♪
♪To the future with you♪
♪I am still♪
♪Waiting through your years♪
Don't move.
♪Who can truly understand
the joy and sorrow of life?♪
♪When will spring flowers bloom again?♪
♪The snow is all over the sky♪
♪How to bury♪
♪Unwavering love♪
You like fireflies?
Don't you like sleeping
with the light on?
The villagers don't
want to waste lamp oil.
so you can hang
this firefly pouch by your bed.
It might help you sleep.
Why are you doing this?
You gave your sleeping powder
to the villagers.
Without it. you can't sleep.
I can't knock you out
every night. right?
I'm the reason they suffer.
I deserve the consequences.
Hurt your hand breaking the window?
Let's go home and treat it.
It's just a scratch.
Don't worry about it.
For a moment. I thought
they were going to...
Why were you so panicked today?
You weren't scared at all
when Wenhua Pavilion caught fire.
I was afraid you'd end up
like my father.
During the Qingzhou fire.
he saved me at the cost of his life.
I watched as he was burned alive.
but he never let go of the rope.
Mei. hold on tight!
- Father!
- Mei!
- You must...
You must survive!
I used to struggle with sleep.
Even a sliver of light
would give me nightmares.
But now.
I don't anymore.
Both the Qingzhou fire
and Zhongshan poisoning
resulted from
the power struggle for the throne.
You.
Wei.
the Xiyan beauties.
and the 100.000 innocent people
don't deserve any of these consequences.
I once valued
the honor of the Weibei Army
above all.
but now I realize
the suffering of the people
far exceeds anything
the Weibei Army went through.
What's done is done.
We have to look ahead.
We both need to learn
to wake up from our nightmares.
Let's go.
It makes the room much brighter.
Sleep well.
Even a lifetime of atonement
may never be enough.
What?
The Crown Prince
is also searching for Mei Lin?
His Highness often says in private
that he doesn't believe
Prince Jing's death
was an accident.
Liu Zhong.
what do you think?
Speak freely.
Your Majesty.
in my humble opinion.
His Highness and Your Majesty
are thinking the same thing.
Both General Yin
and Princess Hengyang's son
saw Mei Lin at Lushan Hunting Ground.
I'm afraid the truth
behind Prince Jing's death
can only be uncovered
when we find Mei Lin.
You sly old fox.
you're just circling around!
Send some Imperial Guards
to secretly follow
the Crown Prince's men.
We must find Mei Lin
before they do.
Your Majesty. do you mean...?
I suspect the Crown Prince
is searching for Mei Lin
to kill her.
Your Majesty.
are you implying
that His Highness
was behind Prince Jing's death?
Liu Zhong.
do you think it's my bad karma
that my sons
have come to this?
Your Majesty.
Prince Jing is already gone.
Even if you uncover the truth.
what good would it do?
Jinghe.
Empress Dejia.
don't blame me.
Born into the imperial family.
this is his fate.
I've walked this same path myself.
As long as the Crown Prince
doesn't jeopardize the nation.
I cannot strip him of his position.
But I must
know the truth!
Your Highness?
What brings you here?
Where is everyone?
Why didn't you report
Her Highness's arrival?
I acknowledge my mistake.
I...
I've overstepped my bounds.
I just
wanted to bring some ginseng soup
to Your Majesty.
The filth and gossip in the palace
are none of your concern.
Don't listen to it.
and don't overthink things.
Yes. I understand.
Liu Zhong.
- Yes. Your Majesty.
- Where's the burn ointment?
I'll fetch it right away.
I know you're worried about Mei Lin.
I've already sent people
to search for her.
If she had nothing to do
with Jinghe's death.
I wouldn't harm her.
But if she was involved.
I don't want you to interfere.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Did I scare you?
Next time I'm angry.
stay away
from me.
We might receive good news
from your brother in Xiyan soon.
No need to be scared.
Go back and rest.
Yes. Your Majesty.
Under the divine envoys' watch.
His Majesty fulfills heaven's will.
blessing Xiyan with peace. prosperity.
and abundant resources
through all seasons.
The people of Xiyan
give thanks to the heavens
and honor our King!
Rise.
The gods revealed in a dream
to His Majesty
that the Left Divine Envoy. Sun Kunlun.
was born into the royal family of Xiyan.
Today. we have
the Second Prince. Yue Chu.
and the Sixth Prince. Yue Qin.
both wise and brave.
We beseech the gods for a clear sign
to appoint the rightful heir
and bless Xiyan
for a thousand generations!
I have seen the will of the gods.
You are the chosen one.
The Second Prince tampered
with the altar.
I will set everything back
on the right track.
[Mingju. General of Xiyan]
It seems the Sixth Prince
is the reincarnation of the Sun Kunlun!
You...!
Father.
the High Priest and Yue Qin
are colluding.
They've
tricked you!
Father.
I would never dare
interfere with divine will.
The Second Prince
disrespects the divine envoys
and will face heavenly punishment.
The Sixth Prince. Yue Qin.
is the reincarnation of Sun Kunlun.
The will of heaven
can not be defied!
Nonsense!
I refuse to accept this!
I'm the Second Prince of Xiyan.
Come nearer if you dare.
The Sixth Prince. Yue Qin.
is blessed by the gods.
He shall ascend to the throne of Xiyan.
Long live the King!
The gods have chosen the true heir!
With divine protection.
Xiyan shall flourish for all eternity!
[Prince Heir's Mansion]
Mr. Yue Qin...
no. Your Highness.
news of your ascension as Prince Heir
has reached Great Yan.
The princess will hear of it soon.
As per your instructions.
we've transplanted
some Qingzhou crops to the estate.
When Mei Lin moves to Xiyan.
she can tend to these Qingzhou crops
to ease her homesickness.
Farming?
Will Miss Mei Lin
enjoy that kind of life?
Madam Wang!
Madam Wang.
The harvest is here!
In a few days.
we'll hold a big feast to celebrate.
There'll be so much delicious food!
Madam.
we'll help you out.
Yeah.
You stay here.
The physician said
you were still weak and needed rest.
Your sister's quick and capable.
Her help is enough.
Listen to Madam Wang.
Don't get in the way.
I'll help too.
I'm all better now.
Thank you. Mei Lin.
Wei.
you still have poison in you.
If you don't rest.
you won't do heavy work again.
Without strength.
how will you make a living?
Exactly. Listen to my brother.
Just rest.
Enough.
You two will just make things harder.
Mei Lin's help is all I need.
Let's get to work.
- Let's go.
I'll help once I fully recover. okay?
Just rest.
♪My heart is actually your♪
♪Rippling♪
♪Past events are like rain.
creating ripples♪
♪Nameless are the flowers and grass♪
♪Heartless is the wind♪
♪Why are we destined to be together?♪
♪It's you♪
♪Who will jump into the deepest abyss♪
♪Stick together through thick and thin♪
♪As long as you can share
each moment with me♪
♪It's you♪
♪Who have witnessed
the joys and sorrows♪
♪Yet you remain as steadfast as ever♪
♪I am♪
♪Your only love♪
♪I am still♪
♪Waiting through your years♪
♪Who can truly understand
the joy and sorrow of life?♪
♪When will spring flowers bloom again?♪
♪The snow is all over the sky♪
♪How to bury♪
♪Unwavering love♪
Mei Lin.
let me help you.
It's alright. Wei.
I've got it.
It's alright. I can do it.
I'm really fine.
Futian's father said I could work again.
Stop working and go rest.
No worries.
Let me help you.
Here. wear my hat.
It's too hot. Put it on.
I don't need it. Wei.
Just put it on.
I'm not hot. You wear it.
I really don't need it.
Erniu.
see that big guy up ahead?
Tell the big brother Erniu did it!
Erniu!
I'll beat you up!
Is it pretty?
Here.
Did you make these?
I borrowed them from Erniu's mother.
The crops can be prickly.
Better put them on.
They fit perfectly.
Your brother sure is capable.
He can even do needlework!
Miss. you're such a lucky girl!
My brother sure is capable.
Thanks for your hard day.
Ergou. let your wife take a break.
Look at her. She's exhausted!
Do it like this.
Make a clean cut.
Like this?
You're weak.
yet you have great strength.
I can't believe
you pulled out the roots too.
Carry the hat on your back for me.
♪The wind scatters the spring flowers♪
♪The dream was filled with sorrow
for the entire night♪
♪Troubled thoughts shatter
into a sky full of stars♪
♪If fate is too unbearable♪
♪I am mired in the mud♪
♪Love is helpless.
falling into the abyss♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope. it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope. it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪
♪If life is a predetermined sorrow♪
♪Love is an endless wandering♪
♪A place in the heart
from which there is no return♪
♪It's a vain hope. it's in imagination♪
♪It's the distinguished light♪